Davies Ilori

Electrical Engineer

Akoka, Lagos Nigeria.

+234-8140772711 daviesilori@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/davies-ilori-13954b18a

I have always had a creative ability and a fascination with how things work, the challenge of solving practical problems inherent in the field of engineering appeals directly to these traits. I am a hard working Electrical Engineer Intern with a strong academic background desiring to further advance acquired skills gained during degree studies and previous work experience. I possess excellent interpersonal abilities and a wide range of technical skills.

Skills

AutoCAD Knowledge Critical Thinking

Interpersonal Communication Technical Knowledge Teamwork Creativity
Organization

Education

University of Lagos

Bachelor of Science: Electrical and Electronics Engineering

Jan, 2018 - Present. Lagos, Nigeria.

Relevant coursework completed:

Instrumentation and Measurements. Fundamentals of Electrical Engineering.

Electrical Engineering Materials. Electrical System Graphics.

Engineering Drawing. Energy conversion.

Experience

Stova Industries Limited.

Industrial Worker

June, 2017 - December, 2017.

Ogun state, Nigeria.

- Used correct personal protective equipment and maintained gear in good working condition.
- Performed general equipment maintenance and repair to minimize downtime.
- Maintained working equipment, power tools and hand tools in operating condition.

Bokasam Resource Itd.

Electrical Engineering Intern

July, 2022 - December, 2022.

Ogun State, Nigeria.

- Participated in the electrical design of a proposed Hostel building housing over 100 students.
- Participated in the electrical design of a proposed Dining Hall.
- Participated in the design of the HVAC system used in the proposed hostel and dining hall.
- Participated in the installation of electrical conduits and outlet boxes.
- Participated in the installation of wires, distribution boxes, lighting accessories and switches.
- Participated in the installation of all electrical appliances.

Programming language and softwares

Html, css, Javascript, c++, Matlab, AutoCAD, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint.